

I'mMhammad Rizwan,a seasoned professional with two years of expertise in Amazon FBA, specializing in wholesale and retail arbitrage.

Additionally, I bring handson experience in Target-To-Sell (TTS) and Walmart operations in the United States. I am confident that my skills and insights can contribute significantly to your organization.



+92 3090338359



house no.105 Habib homes peco road,Lahore



0123mrm456789@gmail.com



https://oxolify.com

MUHAMMAD RIZWAN

Sales Representative

Skills

- Customer support
- Time Management
- Team work
- sales and Marketing
- Client dealing
- Communication

Work Experience

2018-2019

Mirza Shopping center

Sales Manager

 Start working as sales man and than promoted to sales manager and than wholesale distribution manager

2020-2021

Network marketing and MKT call center

Sales representative

• Worked as network marketer with different companies and join call center as sales agent.

2022-2023

CEO OF Oxolify LLC and Qalbi store LLC in Florida

• Worket as VA on Amazon with different clients and agencies in USA and UAE.

Education History

2019-2021

PGC Nankana sahib

• Intermediate degree in medical.

2021-2023

Univesity of central punjab Lahore

• Associate degree in sciences



I'mMhammad Rizwan,a seasoned professional with two years of expertise in Amazon FBA, specializing in wholesale and retail arbitrage.

Additionally, I bring handson experience in Target-To-Sell (TTS) and Walmart operations in the United States. I am confident that my skills and insights can contribute significantly to your organization.



+92 3090338359



house no.105 Habib homes peco road,Lahore



0123mrm456789@gmail.com



https://oxolify.com

MUHAMMAD RIZWAN

Sales Representative

Skills

- Customer support
- Time Management
- Team work
- sales and Marketing
- Client dealing
- Communication

Work Experience

2018-2019

Mirza Shopping center

Sales Manager

 Start working as sales man and than promoted to sales manager and than wholesale distribution manager

2020-2021

Network marketing and MKT call center

Sales representative

• Worked as network marketer with different companies and join call center as sales agent.

2022-2023

CEO OF Oxolify LLC and Qalbi store LLC in Florida

 Worket as VA on Amazon with different clients and agencies in USA and UAE.

Education History

2019-2021

PGC Nankana sahib

• Intermediate degree in medical.

2021-2023

Univesity of central punjab Lahore

• Associate degree in sciences